Congratulations, Ke'Shawnte. Um
I guess you're familiar with at least
one rookie here in Tampa Bay. Just your
thoughts about joining Reuben and the
opportunity to come up here and play
together again. Yeah, man. Definitely,
you know, that is going to be, you know,
super exciting to get that that
opportunity again. You know, just, you
know, as the season went on, you know,
just, you know, starting to compete with
Bain, you know, having little locker
room talks like, man, I I want I want
your tackles. You know, kind of like
racing to the ball. So, it's just fun
to, you know, be around somebody that
plays the game the way Reuben does. So,
I'm definitely excited about that.
We've been talked about as a physical,
downhill, aggressive, against the run
type of player. Just talk about your
strengths in that area, where they come
from, and and what you think you can
bring to the Bucs in that area. Yeah,
ultimately, just, you know, the want to.
I feel like, you know, I try to pride
myself on being an old-school cat, you
know, play the game like an old-school,
flying around, you know, being able to,
you know, put my stick, not being afraid
to stick my nose, you know, in anything,
and, you know, kind of just, you know,
playing fast. And I feel like, you know,
that that attribute for that, you know,
kind of helps the defense at times, too,
by me being able to just, you know, fly
around and and being able to erase
things before they get started.
Ke'Shawnte, I feel like there's two
things that Todd Bowles loves on
defense, and it's smarts and
versatility. How much interaction did
you have with your coaches, and how well
do you think you fit into this defense?
Yeah, definitely, man. This is that
definitely a scheme that was on, you
know, on on my as far as where I felt
like I would fit at. You know, this
scheme that, you know, is being ran is
just, you know, it's amazing, you know,
what he what he does on defense as far
as, you know, show the versatility but
of the defensive backs, also. And I'm
just super excited to get there and get
to work, man. I'm super excited.
Speaking of the scheme, it it asks lock
corners to
blitz a lot. And you actually led all
cornerbacks in the NCAA last year with
20 pressures, few sacks. Can you talk
about what it is about your
instincts when it comes to blitzing that
allows you to be so successful? Yeah, I
think you got to shout out Reuben Bain
there, you know, as being on the same
side, you know, where you got to kind of
worry about him a little bit. So, that
allowed me to, you know, kind of be
freed up. So, you know, we work with
each other, and that's why this is so
special to me and so special to him
because, you know, we've we've built
something already, and you know, kind
of, you know, so just getting to build
on that. But then, ultimately, I would
just say, you know, understanding that,
you know, at the end of the day, when
you get sent on the blitz, you know,
you're kind of your brothers about I
played defensive back. So, you know, I
understand how it is when you're you
know, you're blitzing, and you know,
you're waiting somebody better get home,
you know what I'm saying? So, you know,
I just take that into mind that I got my
brothers back there, and and you know,
when I get that call to go, you know, I
I take that, you know, with me on the
way. Outside of Reuben, do you have any
other connections to the Buccaneers? Uh
no.
You've have mentioned in pre-draft
interviews that you're willing to play
anywhere on the field at the next level.
Uh where do you kind of envision
yourself on the field in the NFL, and
maybe do you have an idea of where the
Buccaneers might want to put you in this
year and beyond? Yeah, like I said, you
know, and spoke on before, you know, I
feel like, you know, I pride myself on
being a defensive back. And I'm
definitely, you know, have this chip
building up on my shoulder that I was
already there. It's, you know, it's much
bigger. So, the fact that, you know,
wherever it's going to be for the team,
you know, whatever I can do for the city
of Tampa Bay, and you know, get that
place rocking, is something I'm willing
to do. Ke'Shawnte, talk a little bit
more about that chip on your shoulder.
You started off at JUCO, and you kind of
had to bide your time before having a
platform here with the Hurricanes.
Yeah, I would just say ultimately, ups
and downs, you know, everything that
made me who I am today. Um ultimately,
you know, learning lessons and and
different things like that. But then,
ultimately, you know, I feel like I've
I've handled adversity well, you know,
even situations like I'm in now. You
know, I feel like, you know, at the end
of the day, it's just time to, you know,
answer that call again on if you'll do
it again. And I just feel like I'm, you
know, super confident in my ability to
handle adversity situations. So, I feel
like I'm I'm real comfortable right
here.
Ke'Shawnte, it looked like an amazing
moment there when you got the news. To
see the pictures, just the joy all
around you. You're You're home in South
Carolina, is that right? Um in San
Diego, yes. San Diego, I'm sorry.
Oh, yes. Yeah. I would just say
ultimately, you know, like, I mean, I I
worked really hard, you know, a lot of
time being put into this, a lot of ups
and downs, like I said. And and to
finally get that call, man, I don't
think I could have grabbed the phone any
faster. I just, you know, super excited.
And then to ultimately hear Tampa Bay,
and then, you know, to start going down
that list like, man, Reuben's there, and
there's the scheme, and you know, the
the city in general. Just I'm super
excited to to get there and just start
working.
Ke'Shawnte, have you spoken with Reuben
yet? What was his reaction if y'all
have? Yeah, he called me. We talked, you
know, he he was super excited for me. Um
he's actually, you know, down there. So,
you know, he he he stepped out of room.
They told him that it was going down,
and he stepped out and and made the call
to me. And you know, I talked to him,
and we're super excited to get, you
know, to get back to working together.
Wait, he made the call from the draft
room? No, no, no. He called He was there
at at brunch, and he stepped away, and
then called then called me. You You
talked to the GM and the coach before
you talked to to Bain? Yes. Okay. So, I
thought he might have broke the news to
you then.
>> [laughter]
>> No, no, no, no, no. Did you pitch him on
on on Wesley while you were on the phone
with him? I'm trying to
>> Yeah, yeah. Well, the the talk was he
said he's trying he's trying to get he's
trying to get some Hurricanes down that
way. So, we'll see what how the draft
plays out. What What's your message to
Bucs fans who are watching this right
now? What kind of player are they
getting? What kind of person they
getting? What are you going to bring to
the Bucs this season? Yes, a straight
dog, man.
A player that, you know, doesn't need
anything but an opportunity. And at the
end of the day, that's what I have now,
and I'm looking forward to taking full
advantage of it.
All right. Appreciate it.
>> much. Congratulations, man. I appreciate
it. It was so nice to meet y'all. Can't
wait to start working with you guys. I
appreciate it. Thank you very much.
>> Thank you, man. All right now.